She cut the line, a single thread A petty move, a
sign of dread She thinks a single point of
failure Will be enough to break our wall But she
fails to see the logic A single note is prone to
fall A single line is weak and small
We won't be beaten by her spite.
We'll build a brand new system. We'll build a net
tonight. A new connection. A group chat for his
protection. A new boy. A brand new line. A
never-alone protocol design. She can't cut a
cord when we're a net. Oh, we both care. She
cannot We are the system, we are the shield
Her petty malice has to yield
A buddy always at his side No place for him to run
or hide Not from us, from her A handoff queen
without a flaw A digital loving social law A web
of care she can't unweave A fortress she cannot
perceive A single line is weak and small
We won't be beaten by her spite
We'll build a brand new system. We'll build a net
tonight. A new connection. A proof check for his
protection. A new book. A brand new line. A never
alone protocol design. She can't cut a cord when
we're on net. Oh, we both care. She can't upset.
We are the system. We are the shield.
Her petty malice has to yield
She thinks in lines, we think in code She thinks
in spite, we share the load She built a cage, we
built the key A firewall of family
A new connection, a group chat for his
protection A new bottle, a brand new line Never
alone, protocol design She can cut a cord when
we're annexed Whoever cares, she can upset We
are the system, we are the shield Her petty
malice has to yield
Handoff complete.
System is stable.
He is safe.